Guide to the Jonathan Huntting Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Notes, Essays, Undated Sermons, 1802-1838; Series III
  - Notes: I Corinthians 6.2, Matthew 12.41 No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - John 14.6 No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - Isaiah 32.5-6 No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - Fragment (No citations) No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - Proverbs 13.13 No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - Exodus 20:16, 17,18; Exodus 20:7 No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - Luke 2:10, 11Luke 17.15-18 (No. 6) No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 299)
  - Luke 15.17-18 (No. 5) No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 300)
  - Luke 15.17-19 (No. 7) No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 301)
  - Job 20.5 No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 302)
  - II Corinthians 6.2 Southold, N. Y., 1 Feb 1832 (Box 7, Folder 303)
  - Notes (Matthew 25.14-30, I Corithians 4.15, Luke 8.18) No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 304)
  - II Corinthians 6.14 No location given, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 305)
  - Notes: Genesis 18.26, Lamentations 2.14, Psalms 11.3, John 15.21, I Corinthians 1.21-23 (1st Dis.), I Corinthians 1.21-23 (2nd Dis.) No location given (Box 7, Folder 306)
  - Ecclesiastes- Funeral Southold, N. Y., 1806 (Box 8, Folder 307)
  - Funeral Notes No location given, 26 Sept 1819- 21 Sept 1838 (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Funerals No. 3 No location given, 20 Sept 1819 (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Funerals No. 5 No location given, 10 Nov 1823 - 18 Nov 18 1827 (Box 8, Folder 310)
  - Small Funerals Notebook No.4 Various locations, 2 June1822 - 7 Oct 1823 (Box 8, Folder 311)
  - Funeral Notes Various locations, 17 April 1812, 12 May 1812 (Box 8, Folder 312)
  - Funerals No. 6 No location given, 26 July 1830 (Box 8, Folder 313)
  - Unposted letter to Mary Williamson Southampton, N. Y., 23 Aug 1803 (Box 8, Folder 314)
  - "Fast Subjects" No location given, 19 March 1817 - 15 March 1821 (Box 8, Folder 315)
  - Thanksgiving Subjects Sterling, N. Y., 22 Nov 1815 - 24 Nov 24 1825 (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - Thanksgiving Subjects No location given, 7 Dec 1826- 12 Dec 1827 (Box 8, Folder 317)
  - Answers to Questions on Divinity No location given (Box 8, Folder 318)
  - Lecture: Matthew 7.13 Southold, N. Y., n.d. (Box 8, Folder 319)
  - New Year's Discourses Various locations, 1 Jan 1817 (Box 8, Folder 320)
  - Dedication of New Meeting House Middledistrict, N. Y., 30 June 1831 (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - Notebook: Doctrine/Credo (Contains Johnathan Huntting's name on book.) No locationgiven, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - Discourse fror the New Year No locations given, 1 Jan 1831 (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - Text Index No location given (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Jeremiah 6.17 Fragment Northside, N. Y., 15 March 1808 (Box 8, Folder 325)
  - Fragment No location given, 20 March 1808 (Box 8, Folder 326)
  - Rev 16, 15 Notes No location given, 28 Feb 1808 (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - Notes No location given, 19 Jan 1808 (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - Notes/ Fragments Sterling, N. Y., 3 Jan 1808 (Box 8, Folder 329)
  - Notes/Fragments Hogsneck, N. Y., 19 Dec 1812 (Box 8, Folder 330)
  - Notes: Luke 14.18 Hogsneck, N. Y., 15 Jan 1812 (Box 8, Folder 331)
  - Notes: Psalm 39. 4 No location given, 16 Sept 1849 (Box 8, Folder 332)
  - Notes: Romans 3.37, psalm 84.13-14, et. al. No location given, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 333)
  - Sermon Notes: Multiple Citations No location given, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 334)
  - Notes on doctrine No location givenq (Box 8, Folder 335)
  - Sermon Notes: Multiple Citations No location given, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 336)
  - Lecture Notes Various locations, 14 Dec 1815 - 12 Dec 1816 (Box 8, Folder 337)
  - Sermon Notes: Proverbs 14,16 No location given, 18 Aug 1808 (Box 8, Folder 338)
  - Sermon Notes No location, n.d (Box 8, Folder 339)
  - Notes -miscellaneous scriptures, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 340)
  - Notes - miscellaneous topics, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 341)
  - Extracts from Knox on education; from Witsens and Rollins (Box 8, Folder 342)
  - Essays: "Let charity begin at home"; "On the improvement of the mind; "Temporal advantages of the Sabbath." (Box 8, Folder 343)
  - Untitled essays, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 344)
  - Student essays: incl. "Ought government to encourage manufacturing"; "Ought the clergy be excused from public office"; "Republican government preferable to monarchy", ca. 1802? (Box 8, Folder 345)
  - Essay, miscellaneous topics - "senior year" (Box 8, Folder 346)
- Collected Material, 1732-1860; Series IV
  - Letters and sermons of others, 1766-1860 (Box 8, Folder 347)
  - Material related to the history of Oyster Bay, Long Island, First Presbyterian Church (Box 8, Folder 348)
  - Material related to St. George's Church, Hempstead, Long Island (Box 8, Folder 349)
  - Land deed, 1732 (Box 8, Folder 350)
  - Printed material - sermons by others (Box 8, Folder 351)